# **Dario Passariello**

Victoria, British Columbia

Tel: +1-778-318-2645 | email: dariopassariello@gmail.com

website: https://passariello.github.io

## **SUMMARY**

Professional developer in JavaScript, PHP, and web technologies. Excellent know-how of multimedia field such as web, illustration, publishing, multimedia productions. Award winning graphic designer and 3d artist specializing in modelling, animation, rendering and mixed reality. Manager in information technology and server administration.

#### **SKILLS**

- Ability to manage multiple priorities and produce results within deadlines
- Good analytical and judgment abilities
- Ability to work independently and as a member of a diverse team, where productive relationships are developed and maintained
- Attention to detail
- Ability to link long-range visions and concepts to daily work
- Take pleasure in team work and employ organizational and managerial skills. Good leadership and ability to involve others, even with a bit of humour. Strong multi-tasking ability and attention to details

- Exceptional understanding of eCommerce, SEO strategies and conversion best practices
- Strong knowledge of the development of mobile and web applications
- Knowledge of website design, development and publication processes
- Knowledge of email and web Analytics / email marketing
- Strong Knowledge of LAN, communications protocols, System Management, Firewall and high end computer equipment
- Knowledge of the principles and practices of marketing and advertising of consumer goods
- Knowledge of marketing digital marketing tracking and Social Media tools

#### **EXPERIENCES**

#### **TRAINER**

## Pacific Design Academy, Victoria, Canada

January 2020 to today

- Trainer for development using WordPress | 12 weeks.
- Trainer for Graphic User Interface and UI | 12 weeks
- Trainer for Server Administration on Linux Server | 12 weeks

#### PRINCIPAL DEVELOPER / UI & UX / IT

## Blue Panda Solution Itd (AppsMoka), Victoria, Canada February 2019 to today

- 1) Development in NWjs for multi OS apps.
- 2) Full stack Dev with PHP and JavaScript
- 3) MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL and JSON
- 4) Server Admin in Linux environment
- 5) Experienced trainer in computer IT
- 6) Strong knowledge in computer IT
- 7) Team leader in small, medium groups
- 8) Mail Server Administrator (smtp, pop3, imap)

- 9) Manager in Jira, Trello and ClickUp
- 10) Strong knowledge of data storage ad control (NAS)
- 11) Network and protocol, web-socket and sockets
- 12) PDF management via PHP
- 13) Experienced developer for reducing amount of reloading in web apps
- 14) Developer in NWjs, Nodejs and SocketIO
- 15) GitLab EE administration / DevOps Operations

#### **EXTERNAL DEVELOPER**

## Cebas Visual Technologies Ltd, Victoria, Canada

December 2018 to today

• Developer – Graphic Designer / UI / UX / MX.

#### IT MANAGER / DEVELOPER

#### Samco Printers Ltd, Vancouver, Canada

June 2018 to February 2019

• Development for internal use of interactive software with last technologies such Electron for storing information and important procedures. Management of equipment for printing and management of protocols such AFP and SMB, AD, Server, Storage, Security and System Administrator

WEB DEVELOPER / 3D ARTIST / ACI TRAINER Digital 3D S.r.l., Palermo, Italy 2011 – 2018

- Excellent 3D modelling geometry skill and creativity for Hard and Organic modelling to create models and contents for medical, military, forensic and media productions for TV, internet in real-time and A/V reality. Also excellent knowledge or rendering field and animation for mechanical and character
- Professional use of Photoshop and Audio-video software for editing with capacity to create and edit images for adapting existing illustrations using of colour correction

PROFESSOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE / 3D MODELLING Fine Art Academy and Engineering University 2016 – 2017

WEB, 3D AND MULTIMEDIA EDUCATOR **Trainer for European Social Fund** 2005 – 2015

OWNER / ART DIRECTOR / 2-D AND 3-D GRAPHIC DESIGNER **Digital Design** 2000 – 2005

- Worked directly with clients to understand needs
  - As business owner understand large workload in tight deadlines
  - During this experience I won the AREZZO WAVE Festival Award in 2004 for best video-clip

## **GRAPHIC DESIGNER / COMPUTER OPERATOR**

#### SELEMA S.n.c

1998 - 2001

- 2D designer and operator for standard and digital printer / plotter in RGB and CMYK
- Image editing and reconstruction of regional photographic archive of Sicily for events and publications

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCES**

2018	Latincouver Association, Vancouver BC, Canada	Web designer / developer
2012 – 2016	View Conference, Turin, Italy	Speaker / mentor
2009 – 2016	ACM Siggraph, Los Angeles, USA	Member of IRC
2009 - 2010	Autodesk User Group International, San Francisco, USA	Member of Board of Directors

## **EDUCATION**

## **Autodesk Inc. | Professional Certification**

Autodesk High Certificate

## **ACI Trainer Certification as Autodesk Certified Instructor**

Autodesk Trainer Certificate

Autodesk Inc. | Autodesk Approved Instructor

**Autodesk Trainer Certificate** 

## IDI Informatica | Office Automation

High EE Certification

## CeFop | Auto CAD and Lisp Developer

High EE Certification

## ITC Lincoln | High Diploma

Accounting and commercial